# GOKHAN ASKIN AWS/DEVOPS ENGINEER Kayseri/Turkey

Phone Number: +905348266316 Gmail: gashcin23@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gokhanaskin/ GitHub: https://github.com/gaskin23

#### **SUMMARY**

Having a strong everyday-learning mentality combined with open-mindness and determination enables me to learn new skill sets and adapt them into new environments faster. Thanks to the working experiences in multicultural environments, being a part of multicultural/multifunctional IT teams with complete coherence is now very easy for me.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# COMMUNICATION OFFICER Turkish Air Force (2017-2019)

- Management Local Network
- Network Administrator
- Consultancy to commander regarding of management communication system

# COMMUNICATION SERGEANT Turkish Air Force (2010-2017)

- Management communication and crypto
- Upload crypto key to regarding device
- Consultancy to communication officer regarding crypto

# **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Python, SQL, HTML, CSS
- Linux, Git, GitHub, Slack
- Cloud(AWS), CloudFormation,RDS,CLI
- AWS S3,ELB,EC2
- Cisco network
- Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving
- Motivation
- Initiative
- Leadership

#### **PROJECTS**

- Phonebook Application (Python Flask) deployed on AWS Application Load Balancer with Auto Scaling and Relational Database Service using AWS Cloudformation
- The Roman Numerals Converter Application aims to convert the given number to the Roman numerals. The application is to be coded in Python and deployed as a web application with Flask on AWS Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) Instance using AWS Cloudformation and CLI Services.
- Kittens Carousel is a static website application deployed with Apache Web Server on AWS Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) Instance using AWS Cloudformation Service.

# **AWS Hands-On Experience On;**

• EC2, CloudFormation, DynamoDB, S3, EFS, CloudWatch, RDS, MariaDB, ALB with ASG, Apache, Nginx, Snapshots, Volumes, VPC, WordPress, IAM, AMI.

## **EDUCATION**

•	Clarusway It Training School	School of The Arts	(2021-2022)
•	Erciyes University	Computer Engineer	(2021-2024)
•	Erciyes University	Law School	(2019-2021)
•	Erciyes University	Law Master	(2021- 2023)
•	Turkish Air Force NCO College	Communications Systems	( 2008-2010)

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Cisco Certified Entry Networking Technician (CCENT)
- Cisco Certificated Network Associate (CCNA)
- AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials Day
- Soft Skills for IT (Great Learning)
- Introduction to Corporate IT Strategy and Business Frameworks (Alison)
- AWS Technical Essentials Day
- Cloud Foundations (Great Learning)
- AWS for Beginner (Great Learning)

## LANGUAGES:

English